const questionList = [
  {
    id: 0,
    question:
      "Name Something People Used To Do At A Younger Age, That Nowadays They Do When They’re Older",
    answers: ["Get Married", "Drink", "Work", "Become Parents"],
    correct: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What Might A Babysitter Want To Know",
    answers: ["Pay", "How Many Kids", "Hours", "Ages Of Kids"],
    correct: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Name Something You Have Seen Added To Jello",
    answers: ["Water", "Fruit", "Whipped Cream", "Alcohol"],
    correct: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "What Might A Tv Not Work Without,",
    answers: ["Remote Control", "Power", "Cable", "Antenna"],
    correct: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "Past Or Present, Name A TV Couple Whose Marriage You Don’t Want To Emulate.",
    answers: [
      "Al/ Peggy Bundy",
      "Homer/Marge Simpson",
      "RoseAnn/ Dan Conner",
      "Archie/Edith Bunker",
    ],
    correct: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "In What State Would You Like To Retire",
    answers: ["Florida", "California", "Hawaii", "Arizona"],
    correct: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "In Which Profession Wear Sweat Pants",
    answers: ["Gym Teacher", "Personal Trainer", "Janitor", "Babysitter"],
    correct: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Name A Sign Of Aging That Is Attractive",
    answers: ["Gray Hair", "Wrinkles", "Wisdom", "Baldness"],
    correct: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Name Famous Department Store In New York City",
    answers: ["Macy", "Saks", "Bloomingdales", "Barneys"],
    correct: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Where Do You Put Presents So They Aren’t Found Before Given",
    answers: ["Closet", "Attic", "Under Bed", "Basement"],
    correct: 2,
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Name A Place People Cram Into",
    answers: ["Elevator", "Car", "Public Transit", "Bathroom"],
    correct: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "Safety Advice Parents Give Kids",
    answers: [
      "Don’t Talk To Strangers",
      "Look Both Ways",
      "Wear Helmet",
      "Be Careful",
    ],
    correct: 0,
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "Place Hot Dogs Are Often Served",
    answers: ["Fair", "Fast Food", "Street Corner", "Beach"],
    correct: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "Animal You Would Not Want To Encounter Hanging From Tree",
    answers: ["Snake", "Monkey", "Bat", "Bear"],
    correct: 0,
  },
];

export default questionList;
